<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Dev-Mex - root</title><link href="https://mvaldes14.github.io/blog/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://mvaldes14.github.io/blog/feeds/root.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://mvaldes14.github.io/blog/</id><updated>2020-08-26T00:00:00-05:00</updated><subtitle>IT Things.</subtitle><entry><title>Pihole is pure awesomeness</title><link href="https://mvaldes14.github.io/blog/pihole-is-awesome.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-08-26T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-08-26T00:00:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Miguel Valdes</name></author><id>tag:mvaldes14.github.io,2020-08-26:/blog/pihole-is-awesome.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Pihole is a great must have in your &lt;span class="caps"&gt;LAN&lt;/span&gt; to block ads and malicious&amp;nbsp;sites.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Its been months ever since I setup my pihole and I never noticed how much it helps reduce the number of ads and spam I used to see in the webpages until one day the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;SD&lt;/span&gt; card on my raspberry pi was at 100% so everything running in there stopped responding and I never noticed it&amp;#8230;. dont be like me and monitor your devices, anyways I started seeing a bunch of pop ups, modals and ads everywhere&amp;#8230; That&amp;#8217;s when I realized once again how much everyone needs a pihole in their Network and also how infected the internet is&amp;#8230; of just so much random stuff that tracks you and serves&amp;nbsp;trash.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So figured since I ended up adding a second pihole to my network as a contingency in case the main one runs into issues again I should tell you how awesome the pihole is and why you need&amp;nbsp;one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The concept of a pihole is quite simple, to block all &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DNS&lt;/span&gt; requests to known malicious and ad provider endpoints, giving you virtually an ad free and safe browsing experience. This is accomplished by turning a device (machine/vm/container) into a &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DNS&lt;/span&gt; server and pointing all your devices to use it as an&amp;nbsp;upstream.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One thing to note is that there are certain sites like YouTube that basically inject the ad into the video feed so blocking it might effectively block you from watching videos so do keep that in mind if your sole purpose was to stop YouTube from serving you ads, this won&amp;#8217;t work. A shame but &lt;span class="caps"&gt;FYI&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another fantastic thing of this project is that the ad lists are maintained by the community so if you notice that a device of yours is doing some extraneous calls and block it you can contribute that domain for everyone to benefit. Trust me once you have a pihole running and you review your traffic from your devices you will notice how much certain things like smart TVs and WiFi cameras make requests every couple minutes or seconds to weird&amp;nbsp;domains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Easier to show you the benefits, like a good ol&amp;#8217; before and after type of&amp;nbsp;deal&amp;#8230;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="pihole-before" src="https://mvaldes14.github.io/blog/images/posts/pihole-before.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aaaaaaand they&amp;#8217;re&amp;nbsp;gone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="pihole-after" src="https://mvaldes14.github.io/blog/images/posts/pihole-after.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So you are convinced how do you get started, you ask?. Well following the installation depending on the device you want to run it&amp;nbsp;on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lazy one line&amp;nbsp;installer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;div class="highlight"&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;curl -sSL https://install.pi-hole.net | bash&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Via docker-compose, in my case I do not use my pihole as &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DHCP&lt;/span&gt; but you can do that if you want&amp;nbsp;to.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;div class="highlight"&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class="k"&gt;version&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="ss"&gt;&amp;quot;3&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class="o"&gt;#&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="k"&gt;More&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="n"&gt;info&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="k"&gt;at&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="n"&gt;https&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;//&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;github&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;pi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;hole&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;docker&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;pi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;hole&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;/&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="k"&gt;and&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="n"&gt;https&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;//&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;docs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;pi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;hole&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;net&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="n"&gt;services&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="n"&gt;pihole&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="n"&gt;container_name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="n"&gt;pihole&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="n"&gt;image&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="n"&gt;pihole&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;pihole&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;latest&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="n"&gt;ports&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class="o"&gt;-&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="ss"&gt;&amp;quot;53:53/tcp&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class="o"&gt;-&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="ss"&gt;&amp;quot;53:53/udp&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class="o"&gt;-&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="ss"&gt;&amp;quot;67:67/udp&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class="o"&gt;-&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="ss"&gt;&amp;quot;80:80/tcp&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class="o"&gt;-&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="ss"&gt;&amp;quot;443:443/tcp&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="n"&gt;environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class="n"&gt;TZ&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s1"&gt;&amp;#39;America/Chicago&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class="o"&gt;#&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="n"&gt;WEBPASSWORD&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s1"&gt;&amp;#39;set a secure password here or it will be random&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="o"&gt;#&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="n"&gt;Volumes&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="n"&gt;store&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="n"&gt;your&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="k"&gt;data&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="k"&gt;between&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="n"&gt;container&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="n"&gt;upgrades&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="n"&gt;volumes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class="o"&gt;-&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s1"&gt;&amp;#39;./etc-pihole/:/etc/pihole/&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class="o"&gt;-&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s1"&gt;&amp;#39;./etc-dnsmasq.d/:/etc/dnsmasq.d/&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="o"&gt;#&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="n"&gt;Recommended&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="n"&gt;but&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="k"&gt;not&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="n"&gt;required&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;DHCP&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="n"&gt;needs&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="n"&gt;NET_ADMIN&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="o"&gt;#&lt;/span&gt;   &lt;span class="n"&gt;https&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;//&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;github&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;pi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;hole&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;docker&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;pi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;hole&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;#&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;note&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="k"&gt;on&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;capabilities&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="n"&gt;cap_add&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class="o"&gt;-&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="n"&gt;NET_ADMIN&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="k"&gt;restart&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="n"&gt;unless&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;stoppe&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;With the package or container running, you can visit the web interface at port 80, you should see something like&amp;nbsp;this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="pihole-panel" src="https://mvaldes14.github.io/blog/images/posts/pihole-panel.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now its time to send all of your &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DNS&lt;/span&gt; traffic to the pihole, the easiest way is to tell your router to send all traffic to the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;IP&lt;/span&gt; of the machine/device running the service but I&amp;#8217;ve found that most of the times the actual computers in your network might not want to really send the traffic via pihole so its easier to force&amp;nbsp;them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have couple &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UNIX&lt;/span&gt; machines simply modify your &lt;code&gt;/etc/resolv/conf&lt;/code&gt; and add the&amp;nbsp;nameserver&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="highlight"&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;# /etc/resolv.conf&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="err"&gt;nameserver &amp;lt;ip-device-or-container&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;On windows you have to do it using the ipv4 settings in the network panel as shown&amp;nbsp;below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="pihole-dns-setup" src="https://mvaldes14.github.io/blog/images/posts/pihole-dns-setup.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If everything is done right you should see something similar to mine that indicates that most of the devices are sending traffic to the PiHole, a quick way to ensure it&amp;#8217;s really working is to visit any site you want and see if that domain appears in your log. So if I visit my own blog I&amp;#8217;d end up seeing&amp;nbsp;this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="pihole-test" src="https://mvaldes14.github.io/blog/images/posts/pihole-test.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The final and fun part is adding domains you want to block to your PiHole, so inside your admin panel go to &lt;code&gt;Group Management &amp;gt; Adlists&lt;/code&gt; and start adding away, one great place to get lists is reddit or this &lt;a href="[https://firebog.net/](https://firebog.net/)"&gt;site&lt;/a&gt;. Do not forget to update your settings after adding some lists by going to &lt;code&gt;Tools &amp;gt; Update Gravity&lt;/code&gt; which effectively reads those Adlists and adds them to your local PiHole. It is recommended you update your lists frequently in case the owners or maintainers add more stuff to it. I&amp;#8217;m quite happy with mine that contains 860K domains and I rarely see issues while loading pages with&amp;nbsp;those.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span class="caps"&gt;BONUS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: If you ever want to mess around with your family go ahead and block facebook and instagram, let me know how that played out for&amp;nbsp;you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, hope this all made sense, if not please feel free to tell me why this sucked on my social media that you can find down below. See ya next&amp;nbsp;time!&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="root"></category><category term="pihole"></category><category term="container"></category><category term="tool"></category></entry><entry><title>Windows is decent again?</title><link href="https://mvaldes14.github.io/blog/windows-decent-again.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-07-19T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-07-19T00:00:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Miguel Valdes</name></author><id>tag:mvaldes14.github.io,2020-07-19:/blog/windows-decent-again.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Windows can do what&amp;nbsp;now?&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="winfetch" src="https://mvaldes14.github.io/blog/images/posts/winfetch.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Been using windows again for almost 2 months now and I gotta hand it to them, it has improved &lt;strong&gt;quite a lot&lt;/strong&gt;. Last time I had it installed on my system was around 2017 when at some point I wanted and needed to play more with the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;LINUX&lt;/span&gt; operating system for work purposes so I could understand it more and honestly I was a bit tired of the constant updates that took forever&amp;#8230; additionally had always been tempted to make the switch so I backed up everything and kissed goodbye to my old &lt;span class="caps"&gt;OS&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did miss the one windows perk which was playing &lt;span class="caps"&gt;AAA&lt;/span&gt; games, at the time I was super into &lt;span class="caps"&gt;PUBG&lt;/span&gt; and it was and I believe still is unplayable in Linux but soon after something called &lt;strong&gt;Proton&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;#8230;started to pop up more and more, turns out at the beginning of 2020 I could play almost *everything* in my Steam library using my Linux &lt;span class="caps"&gt;OS&lt;/span&gt; except couple new and fancy games that I was dying to play and couldn’t be emulated properly, so I entirely blame the switch on Doom Eternal and &lt;span class="caps"&gt;COD&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;Warzone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I downloaded a copy of windows and created the image on a boot drive and so it began… wiping the drives and installing Windows once again, it took almost 30 minutes including the number of restarts it has to do to make sure everything is done properly and setting up the accounts and whatever else it does, finally it was complete and I was presented with a fresh copy of Windows, it still had a bunch of bloatware I did not need and I still feel it shouldn’t even be installed on the system to begin with but that’s for another day. Now I do have to add, I kept using the Windows at work and with new additions like &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WSL&lt;/span&gt; the switch was even more tempting cause I could use it without being blocked by company policies in the work&amp;nbsp;equipment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the great perks of Linux distributions is the package managers (yum, apt, pacman, etc) which is something that I always wished windows would have so I could &lt;a href="https://mvaldes14.github.io/blog/ansible-boostrap.html"&gt;automate everything like I did before&lt;/a&gt;. So googling around I found that windows is already working on it’s own &lt;a href="https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/package-manager/"&gt;package manager&lt;/a&gt; which was awesome but for the meantime I also found chocolatey so I quickly looked up my most common apps and installed them incredibly easy, no need to download a bunch of installers or to get them from dubious sites, again in a matter of minutes my system was&amp;nbsp;ready.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An extra item I did not expect was that the Windows Terminal was &lt;strong&gt;pretty decent&lt;/strong&gt;, I mean it&amp;#8217;s not going to compete against Konsole in &lt;span class="caps"&gt;KDE&lt;/span&gt; but for being their first try it&amp;#8217;s damn good, you can blur the background, change the colorscheme, use custom fonts and it has tabs that take you directly into a &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WSL&lt;/span&gt; distro, once again, very impressed. I have uploaded my personal configuration file to my &lt;a href="https://github.com/mvaldes14/dotfiles/tree/master/windows-terminal"&gt;dotfiles&lt;/a&gt; in case you are&amp;nbsp;curious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cherry on top was installing &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WSL&lt;/span&gt;, by the time I switched &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WSL2&lt;/span&gt; had just come out so I enabled it and installed it, got docker running on top of it and got 2 distros to play with (Ubuntu 20.04 and Kali), hell I even ran my ansible playbooks against one of the distros just to install some software as well and everything was working as expected, I was honestly shocked at how good the performance was, I mean I’m not doing hardcore stuff but to have my containers running over and all of my software dev kit installed and running from &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WSL2&lt;/span&gt; into windows was just magnificent. This post was written in Vscode running in Windows but connected to a &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WSL2&lt;/span&gt; backend, how crazy is&amp;nbsp;that!?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the end I had it &lt;strong&gt;all&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I could play my &lt;span class="caps"&gt;AAA&lt;/span&gt; games like Doom and &lt;span class="caps"&gt;CODWZ&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I could quickly jump into my &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WSL2&lt;/span&gt; Distros to play and try new&amp;nbsp;technology.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I can install a lot of things from the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;CLI&lt;/span&gt; using chocolatey and I&amp;#8217;ll be waiting for the Windows official&amp;nbsp;version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I have a pretty good looking&amp;nbsp;terminal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m honestly very pleased with it now and with the amount of things coming down the pipeline for windows I am for once excited about the future of it, like running &lt;span class="caps"&gt;GUI&lt;/span&gt; apps from within &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WSL&lt;/span&gt;, the package manager and if they clean up their privacy stuff I believe it could start pulling some of the market of users like me that want to develop things but also enjoy playing some good&amp;nbsp;games.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="root"></category><category term="windows"></category></entry><entry><title>Blog 2.0</title><link href="https://mvaldes14.github.io/blog/blog-post-1.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2019-01-21T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2019-01-21T00:00:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Miguel Valdes</name></author><id>tag:mvaldes14.github.io,2019-01-21:/blog/blog-post-1.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;New Year, New blog? Why not&amp;#8230;.It&amp;#8217;s free so &lt;span class="caps"&gt;YOLO&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h1 id="launch-v20"&gt;./Launch&amp;nbsp;&amp;#8212;v=2.0&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometime last year I was dead set on starting to blog but then life hit me hard in a positive way. My baby girl was born, got a new project in a different city so I had to move across the country&amp;#8230;that was an adventure on it&amp;#8217;s own. So between setting my life up again, getting to know people and learning all sorts of new things for my role I completely forgot about the blog not to mention that now that I&amp;#8217;m a dad I love spending my free time with my baby&amp;nbsp;girl.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still the blog was still in the back of my mind so for this 2019 instead of making it part of my &amp;#8216;New Year Resolution&amp;#8217; which to be honest I never fullfil, decided to just &lt;span class="caps"&gt;YOLO&lt;/span&gt; do it. But this time it was going to be more &amp;#8220;me&amp;#8221; if it makes sense and since I now know more on how Python/&lt;span class="caps"&gt;HTML&lt;/span&gt;/&lt;span class="caps"&gt;CSS&lt;/span&gt;/&lt;span class="caps"&gt;JS&lt;/span&gt; work I came up with a new theme and everything customized to what I wanted (some things are still pending like mobile navigation but I&amp;#8217;ll get to it,&amp;nbsp;promise!).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are a number of blog posts I will share with everyone and some of them include some of the new tools that I&amp;#8217;m using at work so it should be&amp;nbsp;fun.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="root"></category><category term="blog"></category></entry></feed>